If you want to get licked from the top
to the bottom from your head to your
toes, baby, you need this.
Hello, baby dolls. Welcome back to the
channel. Or if you're new here, welcome.
I've actually got a couple new recent
subscribers. I noticed on my last video
a bunch of new people were coming from
my last video. So, hey y'all. How are we
feeling today? I'm feeling good. I am
feeling great. Today we are doing a
little hygiene shopping. I need a
restock. I need a hygiene refresh. I
haven't been shopping for hygiene
products in
a pretty a pretty long time. All of my
stuff is low. So, I figured I would take
you guys along with me to go restock and
re-up because I do get a lot of hygiene
questions. So, that'll just help out,
too. And yeah, I just need to update my
stuff. I started getting ready, but I
was like, you know what? Let me get
ready with y'all.
Um I kind of did my makeup a little bit.
But, I added a little lash cluster, for
real. Got my little makeup bag. I'm
really just running errands, but y'all
know me. I like to romanticize, get
ready, slow mornings, just everything
cute. I'm wearing pink today. I have
this little pink tank top that I got
from Fashion Nova. And then I got these
super cute jean shorts. I honestly
thought they were going to be way
longer, but they're not. But, it's okay.
We're just running errands. But, it's so
humid here in Dallas. So, it's fine.
It's literally like so hot, you guys. I
mean, you start sweating. And it's like
raining. It's just it's gross. So, I
need as less clothes as possible. Also,
today we're going to do like a girly
chat. I know you guys want to see my
car. So, I'm going to do a little
Porsche blog or whatever. We'll sit in
the car. We'll talk. I kind of want to
give some like feminine advice and stuff
because you guys ask me the most about
feminine hygiene, curly hair,
my car,
what I do for content creation. So,
we're just going to talk about all of
the things, okay? Another episode,
another weekly vlog with Jay. Okay,
that's what today's going to be cuz I
feel like I'm all over the place. Every
time I start my videos, I'm like, what
do I talk about? What do I say? But,
I'm just
Let's just chill. Let's just be normal,
okay? First thing, y'all, I found this
new lip oil from Farmasi and I swear
it's like so freaking soft and
ooh, it's like creamy.
Makes my lips so freaking plump and it
smells like honey. It's so good. And
then I also have my Naturium I'm going
to spray just a little bit.
This is what I say, hydration mist.
Makes you look really glowy. Mhm. Shout
out Naturium. I love Naturium. We're
going to purchase a new Naturium. I'm
out of my Naturium body wash. I don't
even know if I'm saying it right.
Naturium? Naturum?
How do you guys pronounce Naturium? Let
me know in the comments because
they be eating me up in the TikTok
comments whenever I mispronounce
something. I said La Roche Posay, the
the skin care brand was a Korean skin
care, but it's definitely French and
they were eating my ass up in the
comments. So,
um I don't know what I'm going to do
with my hair today, y'all. It's kind of
just out today. I feel like I don't
really need to do it for real because
we're just going to run some errands,
but I had it in this headband. Let's see
how it looks.
Let's fluff her out. Let's fluff her out
and see. Ooh.
Yeah, I don't know.
We might have to style it.
Looks a little crazy. But anyways,
how are y'all doing? It's mid-April.
It's kind of like the end of April.
April showers bring May flowers. How are
we feeling about spring? I'm low-key
ready for summer. Like this summer I'm
going to be on a yacht. I'm going to be
out the country. I'm going to be all
over the summer like for real, I'm so
ready for the summer. Like I don't know
what it is. It's something in the air,
but
it's literally something in the air,
[\h__\h] I took a month off from YouTube
and now I'm just ready to get back in
the field like
y'all, we're about to have so much fun
this summer and you guys are coming
along with me every step
of the way, mostly.
As much as I would I want y'all to, but
I feel like I haven't talked to y'all in
so long, so So have so much to like say.
This hair is actually crazy. I honestly
might just style my hair off camera
because honestly we need to go. I kind
of want to get my day started. I'm
hanging out with my friends later. We're
doing a little spades tournament. Me and
my friends have been heavily heavily
into spades lately. So
yeah, I just want to go ahead and get
this video out for you first cuz you
know I'm work and then play, not vice
versa, okay? So I'm about to get
dressed, do my hair,
come back, we'll do a little bit of
finishing touches and then we can go.
Here is the fit. I don't know if you
guys can see for real, but
it's very cute. It's just a simple
little
girly vibe.
And then for my hair I did half up half
down.
That's what I did and then for jewelry I
did a little necklace, my earrings of
course, never leave the house without
your ring right here, okay? And then I
have my watch.
And for shoes
I'm going to do my spring, my cute
spring and pink Christian Dior sandals.
It just It goes perfect with the outfit
like come on. And then I'm going to add
a little bit of my Fenty Skin body milk.
I love this stuff. It's so good.
Like Fenty Skin is really that girl.
Like look at the glow you get. It's
amazing.
If you don't have Fenty Skin, try it.
It's really good. I'm sure you guys will
love it. It smells amazing. It's like
vanilla. All my vanilla girlies,
Fenty Skin?
Yes.
And then for perfume, I'm going to do my
pink Miu Miu. This is in L'Eau Bleue
Rose.
Just spritz a little
a lot everywhere.
Back of my knees, neck, here,
just everywhere, okay? I'm going to be
smelling so good walking through this
store. Bag of choice is my little
product to match my sandals, so I'm
ready.
So, come on, let's go.
Okay, boom. We've made it to Target.
Y'all, the lighting in here
absolutely makes me look like a
washed-up rug, but it's okay. I have my
little mic.
So, hopefully you guys
can hear me well. First order of
business is my favorite, which is body
care. And there the selection here is
OD. I feel like they just restocked or
something. Now, in my personal
opinion, Neutrogena is the best body
wash out there right now. This is what
I'm repurchasing. I need it. It's my
favorite. It makes me so soft and glowy.
This is one of my favorite products
ever, ever, ever.
And then they have this one, too. I
don't really use this one, but I know a
lot of people have seen good benefits.
But also, this one. If you can find
this, you need to grab it, because if
you have backne, any acne on your face,
anywhere on your body, this is what you
need.
Thank me later. Since I double cleanse,
I get one that's like good for my body,
and then I get a body wash that's like
good smelling and soft that I really
like.
So, I usually use the Dove.
I've been using the Shea butter Dove
one. I really love Dove. It makes you
really soft. I love this
scent. I love this
scent that I'm going to try.
So, adding this to the cart.
Another honorable mention for the body
washes is the Method body washes for a
cheaper option. If you guys want to go
the little
cheaper route or if you're on a budget,
these get the job done. They smell so
good. I love Method body, and this scent
specifically smells like Jesus himself
wiped your ass for you. Like it smells
so good. I love this one. Okay, so boom.
Now we have body lotions, body creams,
all of the things. And you guys know
already I'm re-upping on my Brazilian
Cocoa Cream.
Yes, leaves me smooth as a baby's
bottom. It's from Palmer's. Also
re-upping on my EOS lotion. Now this one
is the one that I have. This is the best
one, but I just smelled this creme de
pistachio. I haven't tried this. Have
y'all tried this one? It smells so
freaking good. So I'm going to get this
one instead of this, but I usually do
use this one. This one's really good.
I've just been on a vanilla kick like I
don't know.
Wait, has my mic not even been [\h__\h]
working? What? Um
I hope it is. Anyways, if you'd like to
splurge, okay, you don't care about
spending a pretty penny,
then I do suggest trying Hempz
for your lotion. I really love this. I
have like three or four of them, but
they are like really thick and creamy
and they always just make me feel so
moisturized and I love the scents they
have. They have like sweet pineapple and
honeydew melon. They have a pink one
that I really like. They just Hempz is
that girl, okay? I literally don't even
know if my mic is working. Like I can't
tell right now, so
I'm sorry about that y'all if it's not
working. I don't know what's going on.
Like it's like blinking at me and it's
making vibrations, but I don't know
what's going on. I'm just going to have
to scream in here now.
What even gave me the idea to film this
video was so that I need to re-up on my
body oil. That's my favorite, which is
the Shea Moisture Virgin Coconut Body
Oil. Now
if you want to get licked from the top
to the bottom from your head to your
toes, baby, you need this. You need
this. Like it smells so good. Honorable
mention
the illuminating massage oil. I kind of
use this one as a body oil too cuz it
just smells so good and it leaves me
glowing.
But,
the white one is the one that I really
like. These are from Shea Moisture and
they
are my favorite products literally ever.
Moving right along to deodorants, I'm
picking up the Dove spray.
This is my fave, obviously. And then I
also
get Degree as well. I like to have two
because sometimes I like the spray and
sometimes I like to actually rub it on
my body, so it just depends for real,
but I love these ones and these are what
I always use.
Also re-upping on my floss.
This is the one I like.
The double line is really good, too. I
have those as well. Obviously got to get
my TheraBreath.
Duh.
This right here will have your breath
smelling fresh all day. If you know, you
know. If you don't, now you do. Also
re-upping on my Rizos Curls Curl
Defining Mousse. I didn't even know they
had Rizos Curls in Target, but they do.
I also use this. You guys saw that in my
last video. Or actually, no, you saw
this on my Instagram. I don't know, but
yeah. Ooh, they have Pillow Soft Curls,
too. I love. Best hair oil on the
market, just saying. Massage it into
your scalp twice a week and thank your
girl later. Only 9 bucks. I just think
as a woman you can never have enough
cotton pads, like
never. Just never. Also, ladies, I
picked up some organic tampons. I know
we talked about these in my last hygiene
video and I picked them up just trying
them cuz I didn't know
how well organic tampons would work down
there. Do you guys use organic or
regular? Because I feel like the regular
ones are not good for us at all. I don't
know what they're putting
down there in these tampons, but it's
It's good for us. And so I tried the
organic route. Um some people like to
douche. Some people just don't even wear
tampons.
What do y'all do? I don't know what is
the best route for us like
as women,
there what is good for us? Literally,
what is good for us?
But, this is what I've been using. Let
me know if you guys like these, if
you've tried them. Let me know what
brand you use
of tampons or pads or whatever.
Any better alternative to the [\h__\h]
that we trying to Okay. The camera is
about to die. I need to go in the car
and charge it, but also getting my
micellar water because I love her. Ooh,
I'm sorry, y'all. My camera died while I
was inside the store, so I had to come
to car and charge it real quick. But, I
was basically finished, so you guys
didn't really miss anything. I basically
got the bulk of what I needed. Now,
there is one product that I was looking
for in the store. I brought my own just
in case they didn't had it, but I was
looking in the store to see if they had
it, but they didn't.
But, I need to put you guys on. If you
struggle with backne,
like me, like I did before I found this
product. If you struggle with any body
acne, anywhere on your body,
specifically backne though, this right
here cured my backne in literally a week
or two. Like a week or two. This is the
Frank Body original coffee scrub. Now,
this is literally just coffee grounds
and almond oil in it. Like it's legit
just
coffee in here. And you rub this all
over your body in the shower, leave it
on for about 3 minutes, wash it off. I
kid you not, I have never felt softer in
my entire life. I really want to work
with them now.
So, I already DM'd them and talking
about a potential collab because I am
obsessed and I actually saw really,
really good results and I cannot stop
talking about this. I've recommended it
to all my friends. Like, now I have to
let my girlies know, but this is like
magic in a bag. I don't know what it is
about coffee that gets rid of like the
dark spots on your skin, but it works.
Like, wow. Like, my life is changed.
Like, you guys know I used to have bacne
all over my back and look how smooth it
is now.
Like, I used to have bacne all right
here and it's just so smooth. Like, I am
obsessed and I just had to let you guys
know. Okay? I don't know how much this
is and I don't even know where you can
get it. I thought they were going to
have it in Target, but they didn't. So,
I brought mine from home like I said,
but they sent this to me in PR and I
don't know. Get your hands on this. Type
it in on Amazon or something. Just get
this. You need it bad badly if you
struggle with acne anywhere on your
body. Like, for real. Not sponsored. I
This is This is crazy. But, anyways,
I heard you guys wanted a little car
tour. So, let's do a car tour. So, boom.
Here's what it looks like when you first
open it. She is a beaut. I'm obsessed
with my car, you guys. It's a little
dirty. Okay, don't mind that. Might need
a cleaner.
But, this is my little setup up here. It
has all the navigation, all of
everything. This is my favorite part.
She's so freaking gorgeous. Like, I just
love the color
of this. I got the tan interior,
obviously.
And it goes on all of my seats. My
favorite little thing about this car is
that it has the Porsche symbol right
here.
It's just cute. And then the back is
It's not super big, I'm not going to
lie, but it's the perfect size for me.
It's very compact.
And then up here is my sunroof, which I
love because it's so bright in here. And
then if I do the little
the little button, she just opens right
up.
And I just love it. Like I'm obsessed
with this car.
Like this is like the perfect car for
me. Seriously, like it's like my little
dream car. Um and I need to add like
some pink lights. I have like my stuff
in here, but I need to add like pink
lights in the bottom and like pink
little just cute liners. I want some
pink lights for like night time. And
just make it like cute and girly cuz
right now it's black and I did say that
I wanted to make my car pink, like wrap
it pink, but I ended up not doing that.
Like I don't want to do that because I
don't want to have like a super high
profile in here. Like I just want to
just mind my little business and when
you open it, then you'll see, oh, it's
like a girl's car. You know what I mean?
I'm just I'm super obsessed with it. And
so
it's my little Porsche Macan and I love
her. It's my little car tour. Oh, and
then on my keys
on my cute little keys I have my little
Hello Kitty thingy. And then I have some
like I don't even know. This is like a
little fake facial mask.
It's so cute. The little Porsche keys
are so cute. And then it's just like a
little button if you press it, it
automatically opens up your trunk for
you.
I have my little wagon in there for my
groceries because I hate taking too many
trips up and down my stairs where I
stay, so I ended up getting me a little
wagon and I just leave it in the back.
For the most part I try to keep this car
clean, okay? I need something for
Mufasa. Every time he gets in the car,
he rides in the trunk because he's not
about to mess up my seats, okay?
We've upgraded, okay? I can't have
his claws like in the seats, okay? F no.
So, I need to get something like in the
back for him to sit. He hasn't really
been in this car that much because of
that reason. But, when he does and when
I do need to take him,
he sits in the back. So, yeah.
But, other than that, I mean, I think
that's pretty much it. Like, I don't
know what else to tell y'all.
You guys see what we're working with
here, you know? But, anyways, I also
wanted to do a little like girly car
chat type of situation because I saw
this video on TikTok and I got inspired.
And we are already doing hygiene
shopping today, so I figured I kind of
wanted to do
my feminine non-negotiables. Like, my
feminine
Like, these are non-negotiables that I
do that I would consider to be feminine,
girly, soft, like, just non-negotiables
that I do. And I want to share them with
you and see if you guys like it and if
you guys can relate, I want you guys to
let me know your non-negotiables. And
these don't necessarily make you
feminine, but it kind of is on that
route. So, these are
my five non-negotiables. I wrote them
down in my notes so I could chit-chat
with you guys
because I'm always one step ahead. Okay,
boom. Even on here, I wrote these are
subjective and just my opinion, so be
nice in the comment section, please.
Okay? Don't eat me up. All right? Do not
eat me up. Okay, so boom. Number one,
you guys probably already know what I'm
about to say, but my number one
non-negotiable is I will never leave the
house without earrings. And I tell you
guys that all the time. Like, never walk
out the house without earrings. I'm
going to tell you why. Because even if
you didn't put any effort into your
look, earrings make it look like you
did. Like, earrings make you look put
together regardless of your appearance,
regardless of your mindset, regardless
of anything. Like,
earrings just make a lady look polished,
in my opinion. Like, I don't know. It's
just something about an earring
that just
it gives that polished look. And also, I
love a statement earring. I love a big
thick statement earring. Now, you can go
a little daintier, keep it cute, simple,
whatever your style is, but always
always always have an earring in. It's
just so girly and feminine, and I just
love it, and it's cute. It's just cute.
Honorable mention, I always have my toes
done.
Like always. Like how am I supposed to
wear a sandal if my toes aren't done?
Okay, I can't be looking crusty and
dusty. No, no, no, no, no. I need a
color on my toe. Right now,
right now we're in pink. Right now we
have pink. They don't actually match my
shirt today. But yeah, I always have my
nails and toes done. Nails can be worked
through. We can do a press-on. We can do
a slight paint. But the toes,
nah, the toes need to be done. I'm
sorry. The toes, they have to be done.
They just do. Even in the wintertime,
even in the wintertime I shave my legs
weekly, and I have my toes done weekly,
even though I'm probably wearing
closed-toe shoes, and I'm probably not
showing my skin too much. I just like to
be well-kept and like taking care of.
You know what I mean? Have all of my
ducks in a row. You feel me? Number two
is I always keep a lip gloss in my
purse, too.
As a matter of fact, like every single
one of my bags, every single one of my
purses that I own has a lip gloss, a lip
balm, a lip oil, something to help my
lips look glossy, moisturized, or
something. I just feel like it's bad
[\h__\h] 101 to have a lip gloss on you at
all times. Like you never know when
you're going to need it. You never know
when you're going to need to reapply it,
or
if you just want like some cute supple
lips, like just being able to pull it
out of your purse at any time
is key. Like that's that's what you
want. Always always have a lip gloss.
And get the cheap lip glosses from
beauty supply and just throw them in all
of your purses. You will thank yourself
so much later. Like
non-negotiable. Non-negotiable.
Always got to have a lippy on me.
Always. Number three, this might be a
little controversial, but I apply my
body oil first and then my lotion. I
never ever apply lotion and then body
oil. So, what I do
and I have very very soft, supple, glowy
skin. So, what works for me, I just do.
I don't really like follow. Like, if
something works for me, it works for me
and that's what I do. I don't care if
other people say put lotion on or not.
Body oil works for me. Ooh, what's going
on here?
My nosey ass. But, anyways, so like So,
what I like to do is when I get out of
the shower and I'm still soaking wet, I
have not even touched my towel to dry
off yet, I put body oil on with the
water that's dripping down from me.
Before I even touch my towel, before
I've even dried off my body, I will
apply body oil and get it into my skin
and let it work and soak up into my
skin.
And then I'll kind of pat dry. I never
really rub cuz if you like rub dry, it
can cause wrinkles and stuff. So, I just
pat myself dry and then I will apply my
lotion once my body oil has kind of set
in my skin a little bit. I apply the
lotion second to seal in the moisture
from the body oil.
And it's just worked the best for me.
That's the best results I see, so
if you've been putting on lotion before
body oil, try the flip side of that and
do body oil first and then your lotion.
But, yeah, I think that's a little tip
for the girlies, just in case you
weren't already doing that. Number four,
non-negotiable is have a signature
scent. Have a Have a signature
something. Have a signature routine.
Have a signature jewelry stack. Have a
signature shoe. Have a signature pant
that you like to wear. Something that is
personal and special to you that always
looks good, no matter what, for you.
Something that you love. Hence, your
signature scent or whatever it is. And
like getting older, finding your
signature scent, finding your signature
lip gloss, finding your signature lip
combo as a girl is just the best feeling
ever. Like let's say you're like in a
rush or something and you have like your
signature outfit that you know is going
to look good on you, bomb as [\h__\h] your
booty look good, it's sitting the
girlies up, or you have a lip combo that
you really like, or you have a scent
that you really really like that
every time someone smells that scent
they think of you because it's your
signature scent. Like it's just
something very special about having your
signature thing about you. Me
personally, I have a bunch of
signatures. Like my signatures kind of
shift shake a little bit. Sometimes I
like vanilla, sometimes I like pink.
Well, nah, I always like pink. But y'all
know what I mean, like
I have signatures, but you can switch
them up. Like it's just
that's the fun part. That's the process
of like finding your signature stuff.
Like it can be changed. You can switch,
you can always go back to a signature
scent that you had like 2 years ago or
something. Like a signature playlist, a
signature song that you listen to in the
morning. Like just something that is
you.
You know what I mean? I think that's
pretty self-explanatory. I'm going to
keep yapping and yapping. I have one
more though. Number five is I just
quickly jotted these down, so that's why
they're like kind of short. If you guys
like this little segment of the video or
want more of my signatures, let me know.
I can do some more. But my last one,
number five, is my house must smell good
at all times. I do not play about
scents. Like I just don't. Like I don't.
I don't. I don't. And people always tell
me how good I smell, how good my house
smells. Like well, you know, my friends
who actually come over and see my house.
But yeah, I don't play about that. I
don't like a dirty house. No, no, no,
no. And then on top of that a stinky
dirty house? [\h__\h] no. Like my house is
always has a candle burning, there's
always a room spray being sprayed, or
it's always like a fresh scent from my
perfumes, from my cleaning products
where I've cleaned, laundry, fresh
sheets, like just good scents going on
in the house. Just like keeping your
space clean is a non-negotiable for me,
personally. Now, I'm not talking about
like clutter, clothes, and like PR
packages and [\h__\h] like that. I'm talking
about like if your space is dirty, it
stinks, and stuff like that. Like,
that's not feminine. That's not That's
not even
like responsible, honestly. My house
just has to smell good. My house has to
smell girly. And I have some friends who
like smoke and stuff, and I
don't let them smoke in my house. Like,
no. They always try to get me to smoke
in the house. I'm like, no. You're
insane. You cannot smoke in my house.
Like, no. My house smells like a girly
angelic princess lives here. And that
would be correct. But, yeah, y'all, that
was my non-negotiables. Let me know
y'alls. Do not leave this video without
letting me know some of your
non-negotiables down below in the chat.
Okay?
I'm watching you.
I'm watching y'all. I might not even
respond to y'all if y'all don't even let
me know what your non-negotiables are.
No, I'm just kidding, but let me know.
Talk to me in the comments. I want some
more. I want some that I can add to my
list. And then I also want to know like
what y'alls are, too. Because people
come from different backgrounds,
different families, different parts of
the earth, different environments. Like,
everybody has different little quirks
and tricks that they can probably share.
So, let me know
what y'all do. Help a girl out, okay?
Did you guys like today's video today?
Hopefully it's long enough. I don't
know. I feel like I've been yapping like
for hours talking to you guys, but
whenever I cut it up, sometimes I'm
like, damn. I could have said way more.
But, yeah. I'm about to go home. I made
some chicken noodle soup last night for
dinner. So, I'm really excited about to
go eat that, and then I'm going to my
friend's house to play spades. Let me
know what videos you guys want to see
from me. I love you guys so much. Enjoy
the rest of your day and like always,
I'll see you next week.